<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ana Reyna</title>
    <link>https://anareyna.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ana Reyna</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 14:26:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://anareyna.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Connecting Hugo with Forestry</title>
      <link>https://anareyna.github.io/blog/connecting-hugo-with-forestry/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 14:26:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anareyna.github.io/blog/connecting-hugo-with-forestry/</guid>
      <description> adsdfsdf
titulo 66 knlkjl  hgjh ihjoi   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ofertop</title>
      <link>https://anareyna.github.io/code/ofertop/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 23:01:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anareyna.github.io/code/ofertop/</guid>
      <description> Responsive e-commerce redesign implementation from scratch for Ofertop. BEM methodology applied and also Atomic design concepts in order to work with components and keep site maintainable and scalable.
Front-end tools:  Pug (HTML preprocessor) Javascript (ES6) Stylus (CSS preprocessor) Gulp.js Bower BEM Atomic design  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freensy</title>
      <link>https://anareyna.github.io/code/freensy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2016 23:01:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anareyna.github.io/code/freensy/</guid>
      <description> Role: UX/UI Logo, site design and front-end implementation for a secret santa (high fidelity prototype) demo project in Spanish. This is a proposal for a web app.
UX/UI tools:  Sketch app Invision app  Front-end tools:  Gulp.js Flexbox (CSS) Stylus (CSS preprocessor) Pug (HTML preprocessor) Javascript / jQuery  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get in touch</title>
      <link>https://anareyna.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2016 13:00:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anareyna.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>You can send me an email or find me on
Twitter, Github or LinkedIn. Thanks for stopping by!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Estilomio</title>
      <link>https://anareyna.github.io/code/estilomio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2016 23:01:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anareyna.github.io/code/estilomio/</guid>
      <description> This is a redesign project for the fully responsive version of this ecommerce site.
Front-end tools:  Gulp.js Flexbox (CSS) Jade (HTML preprocessor) Javascript (ES6) Stylus (CSS preprocessor) Jeet.gs / Rupture (grids and media queries add-ons)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jobs</title>
      <link>https://anareyna.github.io/code/jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2015 23:01:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anareyna.github.io/code/jobs/</guid>
      <description> This is a personal project for a job board demo. Using flexbox, responsive web design, and pre-processors. Designed and implemented from zero.
Front-end tools:  Jade (HTML preprocessor), Jeet.gs Javascript (ES6) Stylus (CSS preprocessor) Gulp.js Flexbox  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning about A/B Testing</title>
      <link>https://anareyna.github.io/blog/learning-about-ab-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2015 11:32:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anareyna.github.io/blog/learning-about-ab-testing/</guid>
      <description>Escrito originalmente en español aquí.
 If you are a web designer, front-end developer, project manager or you have a website you might have heard about A/B Testing, in this post I’m going to explain the basics and see some examples to understand what it is about.
What is A/B Testing? In simple words, an A/B Test compares two versions of a website and then determines which one produces better results at leading your visitors to one of your goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automating sprite creation with Grunt</title>
      <link>https://anareyna.github.io/blog/automating-sprite-creation-with-grunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2015 16:24:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anareyna.github.io/blog/automating-sprite-creation-with-grunt/</guid>
      <description>Visita este link para la versión en español.
 Why should I use sprites in my project? Sprites can benefit page speed in several ways. First, if many small images are combined into one large image, the browser will require fewer server connections. Second, depending on how well the large PNG compresses, this can end up saving a substantial amount of bandwidth. Finally, in some browsers it is faster to decode one large image than several small ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sublime Text Packages to speed up your workflow</title>
      <link>https://anareyna.github.io/blog/sublime-text-packages-to-speed-up-your-workflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 18:15:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anareyna.github.io/blog/sublime-text-packages-to-speed-up-your-workflow/</guid>
      <description>Sublime Text is one of the fastest code editors that has emerged in recent years. It has a great community that produces a lot of packages (or plugins) to speed up the development of your projects. It supports OS X, Linux and Windows platforms.
If you are not using Sublime Text you can find more information and download version 2 here or version 3 (beta) here.
Today we will see some tips and packages that you might find very useful:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GoMobileBI dashboard</title>
      <link>https://anareyna.github.io/portfolio/gomobilebi-dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2014 23:55:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anareyna.github.io/portfolio/gomobilebi-dashboard/</guid>
      <description>Client GoMobileBI (Australia)
Task UX/UI designer
Project Description My task as a UX/UI designer in this project was to target both tablet and iPhone devices. Some of the requirements consisted in the following:
A standardized dashboard look and feel with a flat UI design, consistent with both the new iOS7 look and Windows 8 Modern UI (Metro style).
A mobile-first design approach to support touch gestures. Multiple layouts for a responsive application that adapts automatically to the target device form factors: tablets, smartphones and desktop PCs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qhopper</title>
      <link>https://anareyna.github.io/portfolio/qhopper/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 23:20:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anareyna.github.io/portfolio/qhopper/</guid>
      <description>Client Qhopper (Australia)
Task UX/UI designer
Project Description Q-Hopper is an innovative approach to ordering food from your smartphone. This user interface design has a clean look and feel. The app is intended to be used by fast food consumers in crowded environments like stadiums.

Interactive prototype  Facebook cover design</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interacción Persona-Computador</title>
      <link>https://anareyna.github.io/blog/interaccion-persona-computador/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 20:03:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anareyna.github.io/blog/interaccion-persona-computador/</guid>
      <description>Este es un primer resumen de las clases del curso “Interacción Persona-Computador” dictada por el profesor Scott Klemmer, profesor Asociado de Ciencias de la Computación en la Universidad de Stanford.
Introducción En la Interacción Persona-Computador (IPC) lo primero que debemos tener en cuenta es el humano ya que éste es el que hace el uso del sistema y se comunica con los demás; luego tenemos el computador, que es la máquina y la red en la que se ejecuta el sistema; y después la interfaz, que representa el sistema al usuario.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Gamification Assignment</title>
      <link>https://anareyna.github.io/blog/first-gamification-assignment/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2012 20:15:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anareyna.github.io/blog/first-gamification-assignment/</guid>
      <description>The University of Pennsylvania is offering a Gamification course through Coursera, and this is the first assigment where I share what I’ve learned so far. Here’s the definition:
 You are an employee of Cereals Incorporated, a large manufacturer of breakfast food products. Your supervisor, Madison County, approaches you because she knows you recently took a course on gamification, which she has heard will revolutionize marketing.
She tells you that Cereals Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zapon</title>
      <link>https://anareyna.github.io/portfolio/zapon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2012 23:47:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anareyna.github.io/portfolio/zapon/</guid>
      <description>Client Zapon (Luxembourg)
Task UX/UI designer
Project Description The task for this project consisted on a visual overhaul of zapon.com, a VC funded project based on an interest driven Social Network. The requirements were to make the website as pleasant and user friendly as possible.
Zapon.com is a Social Network based on your interests not specially on friends. By specifying your own interests you can join other people having the same interests to share “links”, “pictures”, “Videos” or chat in real-time with those people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FG global</title>
      <link>https://anareyna.github.io/portfolio/fgglobal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2012 00:05:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anareyna.github.io/portfolio/fgglobal/</guid>
      <description>Client FG Global
Task UX/UI designer
Project Description FG Global is a research platform that works to connect participants with information about upcoming focus group, clinical trials, taste tests, and more, all recruiting in their community. New studies are added daily, and provide participants with the opportunity to share their opinions with hundreds of the world’s most well-known companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>adireto</title>
      <link>https://anareyna.github.io/portfolio/adireto/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 21:39:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anareyna.github.io/portfolio/adireto/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live in America</title>
      <link>https://anareyna.github.io/portfolio/live-in-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 22:19:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anareyna.github.io/portfolio/live-in-america/</guid>
      <description>Client live in america
Task Logo design</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CalidaMed</title>
      <link>https://anareyna.github.io/portfolio/calidamed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2011 21:34:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anareyna.github.io/portfolio/calidamed/</guid>
      <description>Client CalidaMed
Task Logo design</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPerceive</title>
      <link>https://anareyna.github.io/portfolio/iperceive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2011 22:15:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anareyna.github.io/portfolio/iperceive/</guid>
      <description>Client iPerceive
Task Graphic designer
Project Description This is a stationay (business card design)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K&amp;G Architects</title>
      <link>https://anareyna.github.io/portfolio/kg-architects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2010 21:37:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anareyna.github.io/portfolio/kg-architects/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Storenik</title>
      <link>https://anareyna.github.io/portfolio/storenik/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2010 21:44:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anareyna.github.io/portfolio/storenik/</guid>
      <description>Client Storenik
Task Graphic designer
Project Description The target audience for this brochure are art, crafts, clothing and accessories stores that do not have an e-commerce web site yet.The brochure is 8.50 by 10.98 inch page, with a .137 bleed size.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Development Cloud</title>
      <link>https://anareyna.github.io/portfolio/the-development-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2010 22:03:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anareyna.github.io/portfolio/the-development-cloud/</guid>
      <description>Client The Development Cloud
Task Graphic designer</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Javascript Live Certificate</title>
      <link>https://anareyna.github.io/portfolio/sitepoint/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2010 21:54:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anareyna.github.io/portfolio/sitepoint/</guid>
      <description>Client Sitepoint
Task Graphic designer
Project Description The “Certificate of Participation” and the “JavaScript Live Badge” are for participants of the JavaScript Live training course. These guys are people learning JavaScript. Here’s some info about the course that they’ve just completed: http://www.sitepoint.com/courses/javascript-live/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This IT Works</title>
      <link>https://anareyna.github.io/portfolio/this-it-works/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2010 21:52:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anareyna.github.io/portfolio/this-it-works/</guid>
      <description>Client This IT Works
Task Graphic designer
Project Description This project is for a IT company that serves small businesses and non-profits. This brochure is 17×11 with a half fold creating 4 pages
The target audience includes small businesses ranging in size from 10-200 employees, non-profit organizations, and church organizations. They have networks ranging in size from five computers to hundreds of computers and servers. These are mainly businesses that realize the value of outsourcing their IT services or are too small to afford in-house IT services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Armor Games Newsletter</title>
      <link>https://anareyna.github.io/portfolio/armor-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2010 21:41:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anareyna.github.io/portfolio/armor-games/</guid>
      <description>Client Armor Games.
Task Graphic designer
Project Description Armor Games is an online community for casual gamers. This is an email template that promotes their new identity. Yellow and black are the core brand colors.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>